[upbeat music] Come now, why so shy? Just
say our candidates will have your vote
cue-2
and these yellow boys are all your own.
cue-3
Surely a generous recompense for a mere
pittance of effort.
cue-4
No, sir. Though I be not a wealthy man, I
cannot, in good
cue-5
conscience, sell that which is my duty to
sacred crown and country. A man's
cue-6
votes should follow his principles, not
his purse.
cue-7
Oh, why did I marry this fool? What is the
point of him being qualified to vote if
cue-8
he's not prepared to have his votes
bought? He's been offered a handful of
cue-9
guineas if only he pledges his vote, but
he says he's above bribery. Ridiculous. If
cue-10
I could vote, I can tell you I'd be
selling my support to the highest bidder.
cue-11
Thou blockhead husband, gold refuse, when
here's your child in want of shoes.